mobotechie.com 2013-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Mobotechie.com

[Home](http://mobotechie.com/) Privacy Policy

We at Mobotechie.com give prime importance to our users’ privacy and are committed to protecting it always. If you have any doubt concerned with our website [privacy policy](http://mobotechie.com/privacy-policy "privacy policy") or software, please feel free to [contact us](http://mobotechie.com/contact-us "contact us"). Please read our [Privacy Policy](http://mobotechie.com/privacy-policy "Privacy Policy") below to learn more about how we treat personally identifiable information, how it is protected and used.

#### Log Files:

Mobotechie.com does NOT collect any personally-identifiable information, such as name, address, [phone](http://mobotechie.com/tag/phone "phone") number or email address from users of this web site without their knowledge, and takes measures to protect their privacy.

However, like other standard web site servers, we use log files to collect information purely to identify the number of visitors to this web site, what those visitors looked at and how long they spent browsing. These information will only be used to judge the popularity of this web site and to make future improvements. These includes IP address, internet service provider, type of browser, date/time stamp, operating system, referring/exit pages, number of clicks to different pages, time spent on the site, demographic information, etc. These data are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

#### Cookies and/ or web beacons:

A cookie is a small data text file stored in your browser for recognizing you each time you visit a site. Our site doesn’t use cookies. However, some of our advertising partners may use cookies and/or web beacons on our site to collect data in the ad serving process. mobotechie.com has no access to or control over these cookies. However, you can remove them at any time using your browser tools.

#### Third Party Advertising:

We use third party advertising companies to display advertisement on this site. They may use cookies to serve ads on this site and use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

#### External Links:

This web site contains many links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

#### Contact:

For any questions or concern regarding privacy and data usage policy of this website, Please mail to: prajune[at]hotmail[dot]com

[Last edited on 2012 December]
